<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<conversations>

	<!-- Tambourine Gal -->
	<conversation ID="TambourineGalConvo">
		<!-- Start nodes -->
		<node ID="Start" IfHaveQuest="Grave Thoughts" IfNotFinishedQuest="Grave Thoughts">
			<text>
				{{C|This rumbling... We better hurry, friend.}}~
				{{C|We need to hurry, =name=!}}~
				{{C|Please, do as Otho says. I saw who was behind this quake: we'll need to be ready.}}
			</text>
			<choice GotoID="SongGrave1">*Ask =pronouns.objective= to sing a song of inspiration. You will need it.*</choice>
			<choice GotoID="End">*Nod and move on.*</choice>
		</node>
		<node ID="Start" IfHaveQuest="A Call to Arms" IfNotFinishedQuest="A Call to Arms">
			<text>
				{{w|*=pronouns.Subjective= =verb:adjust:afterpronoun= =pronouns.possessive= hat and =verb:give:afterpronoun= you a firm nod.*}}
			</text>
			<choice GotoID="End">*Nod back. You're ready.*</choice>
		</node>
		<node ID="Start">
			<text>
				{{C|Hey there!}}~
				{{w|*=pronouns.Subjective= =verb:smile:afterpronoun= and =verb:wave:afterpronoun= at you.*}}~
				{{C|How are you holding up, =name=?}}~
				{{C|Want to hear a song, friend?}}~
				{{C|Oh, I just finished a new melody! Care to hear it?}}~
				{{C|Let's rest and listen to the wind, =name=. I want to hear the rumors.}}~
				{{C|Hi there!}}~
				{{C|Ah! Sorry, I was thinking of a new song.}}~
				{{C|Hey, =name=.}}
			</text>
			<choice GotoID="Song">*Ask if =pronouns.subjective= could sing for you.*</choice>
			<choice GotoID="End">*You should keep moving. Wish =pronouns.objective= to live and drink.*</choice>
		</node>		
		<!-- Song Nodes -->
		<node ID="Song">
			<text>
				{{C|Of course, =name=! Close your eyes and listen closely...}}~
				{{C|It would be my pleasure, friend. Close your eyes and listen...}}~
				{{C|I was hoping you'd ask! Now, close your eyes and listen carefully...}}
			</text>
			<choice GotoID="Songs">*Do as =pronouns.subjective= =verb:say:afterpronoun=. Allow yourself to see the rythms and drown in the colorful melody...*</choice>
		</node>
		<node ID="SongGrave1">
			<text>
				{{C|I... Yes, you're right. I'll need it, too. Close your eyes, friend.}}
			</text>
			<choice GotoID="SongGrave2">*Do as =pronouns.subjective= =verb:say:afterpronoun=. Concentrate on the rythm. Let the melody pierce your very being.*</choice>
		</node>
		<node ID="Songs">
			<text>
				{{C|*=pronouns.Subjective= =verb:sing:afterpronoun= of a distant land, so far away from Qud: you see a sparkling white landscape, dotted by dark greens of quill-trees; a smudge of orange, where tribesfolk lit a campfire. 

				Simple life. Smiles and fish.*}}~
				{{C|*=pronouns.Subjective= =verb:sing:afterpronoun= of a festival. Reds, yellows and oranges are all around you, swirling like vortices — so easy to lose yourself here. Laughter and banter, trade and barter. Hidden by a scarlet shawl, a watchful gaze peers vigilantly over all and every.

				Ah, it's a Stilt song.*}}~
				{{C|*Rhythmic strikes. Blindingly white sparks of heated metal jump up and down as each strike reaches its destination. There is no place for mistakes in troll-smith's design; his work is impeccable. The strikes continue. Nothing can disturb the master as he finishes his creation.

				A blade of one edge, imbued with secrets of the petal-smith, meant to be wielded by the beetle-masked.*}}~
				{{C|*=pronouns.Subjective= =verb:sing:afterpronoun= of a hamlet in the hills. Greyness of rock interrupted by by splashes of orange and blue. Tall and white, the legion of wind catchers guards the flowery field near the hamlet's entrance. A beaked one sits there, embraced by her hindren companion. They see you, and gesture to stay.

				Perhaps you will.*}}
			</text>
			<choice GotoID="SongsEnd">*Open your eyes.*</choice>
		</node>
		<node ID="SongsEnd">
			<text>
				{{w|*=pronouns.Subjective= =verb:give:afterpronoun= you a warm smile and =verb:nod:afterpronoun=.*}}

				{{C|I hope you liked it.}}
			</text>
			<choice GotoID="End">*Though the song still lingers in your mind, it's time to move on. Express your gratitude for the tinkle-monk's work and wish =pronouns.objective= to live and drink.*</choice>
		</node>
		<node ID="SongGrave2">
			<text>
				{{C|*=pronouns.Subjective= =verb:sing:afterpronoun= of a battle in a black sea. A beam of pure white light punches through the triangular-patterned barrier. The collosal prism is breached, and as it shatters, the beam splits into six colorful stripes.

				This fight is all they know that's right.*}}
			</text>
			<choice GotoID="End">*Open your eyes. Nod to the tinkle-monk. It's time.*</choice>
		</node>
	</conversation>
</conversations>